Guide to the Ambassador Auditorium Collection ARS.0043
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Series 3: Concert Management and Booking Files, 20 boxes (21.1 linear ft.)
  - Concert/Booking Files, 1990-1991 Season:, 31 folders (Box 309)
    Academy of St. Martin-in-the-Fields; Hamilton, Scott; Ni, Hai-Ye; Viardo, Vladimir; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Brion, Keith; Barrueco, Manuel; Waverly Consort; York, Andrew; Canadian Brass; Muir String Quartet; Pirin (Musical group); Parkening, Christopher; José Greco Company; Bychkov, Semyon; Labèque, Katia; Greco, José; Orchestre de Paris; Labèque, Marielle; Chicago Brass Ensemble; Pogorelich, Ivo; Beaux Arts Trio; Watts, Andre; Galway, James; Calloway, Cab; Larrocha, Alicia de; Bream, Julian; Solisti veneti; Kong, Xiang-dong
  - Concert/Booking Files, 1990-1991 Season:, 25 folders (Box 310)
    Folders contain various materials including programs, correspondence, contracts, clippings, reviews, photographs, fliers, and other records related to each performance. [Folders:] (1) Robin Williams, "Plato's Lost Atlantis" [travelogue]; (2) Cicile Licad/Nadja Salerno-Sonnenberg; (3) Benjamin Frith (Rubinstein Competition Winner); (4) English Chamber Orchestra/Pinchas Zukerman; (5) Gewandhaus Orchestra/Kurt Masur; (6) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (7) Thomas Gallant; (8) Larry Elgart, "Hooked on Swing"; (9) Louis Lortie; (10) Dolora Zajick; (11) New England Ragtime Ensemble/Gunther Schuller; (12) Cheryl Parrish [replaced Stanford Olsen]; (13) Mstislav Rostropovich; (14) Juilliard String Quartet/Billy Taylor Trio; (15) Opera A La Carte, "The Pirates of Penzance," with Donald Adams; (16) Pasadena Youth Symphony Orchestra (Ms. Cheryl Mead); (17) Lee Ritenour; (18) David Grisman Quintet; (19) David Brandon; (20) Elisso Bolkvadze; (21) Pasadena Young Musicians Orchestra (Ms. Marlene Schwartz); (22) Irina Smorodinova; (23) Zachary Opera Auditions Finals [Concert]; (24) AFM [American Federation of Musicians] Senior Symphony; (25) 1990-1991 Itineraries.
    Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Gewandhausorchester Leipzig; Masur, Kurt; Zukerman, Pinchas; English Chamber Orchestra; Frith, Benjamin; Salerno-Sonnenberg, Nadja; Licad, Cecile; Taylor, Billy; Opera A La Carte; Adams, Donald; Zajick, Dolora; Lortie, Louis; Hooked on Swing Orchestra; Elgart, Larry; Gallant, Thomas (oboist); Parrish, Cheryl; New England Ragtime Ensemble; Schuller, Gunther; American Federation of Musicians; Billy Taylor Trio; Juilliard String Quartet; Rostropovich, Mstislav; Olsen, Stanford; Brandon, David; Bolkvadze, Eliso; Grisman, David; David Grisman Quintet; Ritenour, Lee
  - Concert/Booking Files, 1991-1992 Season:, 31 folders (Box 312)
    Folders contain various materials including programs, correspondence, contracts, clippings, reviews, photographs, fliers, and other records related to each performance. [Folders:] (1) General 1991-1992; (2-3) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra] 1991-1992; (4) Vienna Johann Strauss Orchestra, cancelled; (5) Lucia Popp; (6) Daniel McKelway; (7) Branford Marsalis; (8) Jean-Bernard Pommier; (9) Masters of Bluegrass [Josh Graves & Kenny Baker Group, Byron Berline and California, Eddie Adcock Band]; (10) Fran and Brooke Reidelberger, "Tahiti & Fiji - Pacific Paradise" [World Travel Films travelogue]; (11) American Youth Symphony [Mehli Mehta, Irina Smorodinova]; (12) Fidelio Quartet; (13) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (14) John Williams; (15) Mostly Duke (Salute to Duke Ellington); (16) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (17) Suzuki Tour; (18) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (19) Guarneri String Quartet; (20) Barry Douglas; (21) Coldstream Guards & Queen's Own Highlanders; (22) Douglas Niedt; (23) Hanover Band; (24) L.A. Guitar Quartet; (25) Les Ballets Africains; (26) Jim Cole, "A British Summer" [World Travel Films travelogue]; (27) Ravi Shankar; (28) Pasadena Area Youth Music Council [PAYMC]; (29) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (30) Roger Williams; (31) Victor Borge.
    Mehta, Mehli; Wiener Johann Strauss-Orchester; Graves, Josh; American Youth Symphony; Marsalis, Branford; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Popp, Lucia; McKelway, Daniel; Reidelberger, Brooke; Berline, Byron; Hanover Band; Reidelberger, Fran; California (Musical group); Baker, Kenny; Eddie Adcock Band; Adcock, Eddie; Douglas, Barry; Williams, John; Niedt, Douglas; Guarneri Quartet; L.A. Guitar Quartet; Ballets Africains; Fidelio Quartet; Borge, Victor; Shankar, Ravi; Williams, Roger
  - Concert/Booking Files, 1991-1992 Season:, 35 folders (Box 313)
    Folders contain various materials including programs, correspondence, contracts, clippings, reviews, photographs, fliers, and other records related to each performance. [Folders:] (1) Susan von Reichenbach; (2) Marilyn Horne; (3) Osborne Brothers/Mac Wiseman; (4) José Molina Bailes Españoles; (5) Academy of St. Martin in the Fields [Neville Marriner]; (6) Salzburg Marionettes; (7) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (8) the Chieftains; (9) Andre Watts; (10) Irina Smorodinova, Big Sandy [Texas]; (11) Doug Jones, "Portraits of the Great Far East" [travelogue]; (12) Big Band Salute to Benny Goodman [Peanuts Hucko, Buddy Greco, Louise Tobin, Ardie Bryant]; (13) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (14) Eddie Daniels/Gary Burton; (15) Opera in Concert [Los Angeles Concert Opera Association, Smetana's "The Bartered Bride"]; (16) Nikolai Petrov; (17) Seldom Scene; (18) Peking Acrobats; (19) the Gathering of the Clans; (20) 15th Air Force Band of the Golden West; (21) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (22) Michala Petri; (23) Tommy Dorsey Orchestra, Big Sandy [Texas]; (24) Ken Armstrong, "Peerless New Zealand" [travelogue]; (25) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (26) Mel Tormé/Maureen McGovern; (27) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (28) 1991 Naumburg Chamber Winner, Peabody Trio; (29) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (30) Hermann Prey; (31) State Symphonic Kapelle (formerly Soviet Philharmonic), [Gennady] Rozhdestvensky; (32) George Shearing; (33) Benedetto Lupo; (34) Carlos Barbosa-Lima; (35) Big Band Dance Night.
    Peking Acrobats; José Molina Bailes Españoles; Marriner, Neville; Academy of St. Martin-in-the-Fields; Burton, Gary; Los Angeles Concert Opera; Petrov, Nikolaĭ; Seldom Scene (Musical group); Hucko, Peanuts; Greco, Buddy; Tobin, Louise; Daniels, Eddie; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Salzburger Marionettentheater; Jones, Doug; Bryant, Ardie; Chieftains; Watts, Andre; Petri, Michala; Prey, Hermann; Peabody Trio; McGovern, Maureen; Tormé, Mel; Tommy Dorsey Orchestra; Barbosa-Lima, Carlos; Wiseman, Mac; Lupo, Benedetto; Osborne, Sonny; Shearing, George; Rozhdestvenskiĭ, Gennadiĭ; Horne, Marilyn; Reichenbach, Susan von; Osborne, Bobby; Osborne Brothers
  - Concert/Booking Files, 1991-1992 Season:, 41 folders (Box 314)
    Folders contain various materials including programs, correspondence, contracts, clippings, reviews, photographs, fliers, and other records related to each performance. [Folders:] (1) Klezmorim; (2) Pasadena Unified School District [All City Instrumental Music Festival]; (3) Cecilia Bartoli; (4) Music from Marlboro; (5) National Theatre of the Performing Arts [Ballet Folklorico Mexicano]; (6) Doc Watson, cancelled; (7) Tom Sterling, "Bermuda" [travelogue]; (8) Alexander Shtarkman; (9) Rockwell Blake, cancelled; (10) Tallis Scholars [Peter Phillips, director]; (11) Ivo Pogorelich; (12) Benjamin Verdery; (13) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (14) Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra; (15) Jubilant Sykes; (16) Berlin Philharmonic Wind Quintet; (17) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (18) Shirley Jones with orchestra; (19) AFM [American Federation of Musicians] Senior Symphony; (20) Mazowsze; (21) Florence Quivar; (22) Herbie Mann & Jasil Brazz; (23) Alison Krauss & Union Station/Nashville Bluegrass Band; (24) Mummenschanz; (25) Pepe Romero; (26) Pepe Romero/Elly Ameling/Susan Greenberg/Los Romeros; (27) Yo-Yo Ma & Jeffrey Kahane; (28) Empire Brass; (29) Carmen McRae, cancelled; (30) Bulgarian State Female Choir [Le Mystere des Voix Bulgares]; (31) Angel Romero; (32) Robin Williams, "Lindbergh's Historic Flight" [travelogue]; (33) 1991 Naumburg Viola Winner, Misha Amory; (34) Patty Andrews/Les Brown [and Band of Renown]; (35) Michael Ponti; (36) From the Heart Benefit Concert - [for Barbie] York; (37) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (38) Zachary Opera Audition Finals [Concert] (Judges' dinner); (39) Pasadena Youth Symphony Orchestra; (40) Stephane Grappelli; (41) Anthony Newman & Company.
    Andrews, Patty; Pogorelich, Ivo; Band of Renown; Verdery, Benjamin; Amory, Misha; Tallis Scholars; Williams, Robin (Robin Douglas); Phillips, Peter; Kahane, Jeffrey; Shtarkman, Alexander; Empire Brass (Musical group); Blake, Rockwell; Brown, Les; Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra; Ma, Yo-Yo; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Romero, Pepe; Philharmonisches Bläserquintett Berlin; Sykes, Jubilant; Mummenschanz (Group); McRae, Carmen; Jones, Shirley; Ameling, Elly; American Federation of Musicians; Greenberg, Susan, flute player; Krauss, Alison; Romeros; Mann, Herbie; Mazowsze (Musical group); Nashville Bluegrass Band; Quivar, Florence; Union Station (Musical group); Grappelli, Stéphane; Romero, Angel; Musicians from Marlboro; Misterii︠a︡ta na bŭlgarskite glasove (Musical group); Bartoli, Cecilia; Ponti, Michael; Klezmorim; Newman, Anthony; Watson, Doc
  - Concert/Booking Files, 1991-1992 Season:, 17 folders (Box 315)
    Folders contain various materials including programs, correspondence, contracts, clippings, reviews, photographs, fliers, and other records related to each performance. [Folders:] (1) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (2-3) Roy Clark/Crystal Gayle [Gayle replaced Clark]; (4) Dmitri Ratser; (5) Opera A La Carte, "The Mikado"; (6) Carmen Or [replaced Alex Slobodyanik]; (7) Pasadena Young Musicians Orchestra; (8) Bill Monroe & the Bluegrass Boys, cancelled; (9) Los Angeles Children's Chorus; (10) Yale Symphony Orchestra, cancelled; (11) Linda Price Trio, Employee Center, for Regional Directors dinner; (12) CAMI [Columbia Artists Management, Inc.] filming in Auditorium; (13) Disney Project [Disney Young Musicians Symphony Orchestra; performance taped for television broadcast]; (14) Patrick Stewart [performance was rescheduled due to "civil unrest"]; (15) Itinerary File; (16) "In Recital at Ambassador" scripts, 1991-1992; (17) Presidential Choices [1991-1992 American Public Radio program].
    Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Rat︠s︡er, Dmitriĭ; Gayle, Crystal; Clark, Roy; Opera A La Carte; Stewart, Patrick; Monroe, Bill
  - Concert/Booking Files, 1992-1993 Season:, 36 folders (Box 316)
    Folders contain various materials including programs, correspondence, contracts, clippings, reviews, photographs, fliers, and other records related to each performance. [Folders:] (1) General Information 1992-1993; (2) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra] General Information 1992-1993; (3) AFM [American Federation of Musicians] Senior Symphony Free Concert; (4) [Chamber] Orchestra of San Luis (Argentina); (5) Kay Starr with Les Brown & Orchestra [Band of Renown]; (6) Dave Brubeck; (7) Marcel Marceau; (8) Prague Chamber Orchestra [replaced Vancouver Symphony Orchestra]; (9) Romeros Duo [Celin and Pepe Romero]; (10) Ensemble Project Ars Nova [Ensemble PAN]; (11) Robin Williams, "Voyage of Columbus" [travelogue]; (12) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (13) Freddie Hubbard with Bobby Hutcherson; (14) Nancy LaMott [replaced David Seering and Susan Whitney]; (15) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (16) Yevgeny Mogilevsky; (17) Carol Channing & Rita Moreno; (18) Fran & Brooke Reidelberger, "Israel!" [travelogue]; (19) Naumburg Piano Competition Winner, Awadagin Pratt; (20) P.U.S.D. [Pasadena Unified School District, choral concert], cancelled; (21) Chet Atkins; (22) Frula in "Tzigane"; (23) Karpatok [Hungarian Folk Ensemble]; (24) Yu Chen; (25) Jean-Philippe Collard; (26) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (27) Keith Brion's New Sousa Band; (28) Marie-Pierre Langlamet; (29) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (30) Christopher Parkening; (31) [Robert] Shields & [Lorene] Yarnell; (32) Ricky Skaggs; (33) Jane Bunnell; (34) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (35) Musica Antiqua Koln; (36) Lucia Popp/Peter Seiffert, cancelled.
    Hutcherson, Bobby; LaMott, Nancy; Mogilevskiĭ, Evgeniĭ; Channing, Carol; Moreno, Rita; Reidelberger, Brooke; Reidelberger, Fran; Pratt, Awadagin; Pražský komorní orchestr; Romero, Celín; Romero, Pepe; Ensemble Project Ars Nova; Starr, Kay; Band of Renown; Brown, Les; Brubeck, Dave; Brion, Keith; American Federation of Musicians; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Atkins, Chet; Vancouver Symphony Orchestra; Collard, Jean Philippe; Marceau, Marcel; Langlamet, Marie-Pierre; New Sousa Band; Shields, Robert; Parkening, Christopher; Bunnell, Jane; Yarnell, Lorene; Musica Antiqua Köln; Skaggs, Ricky; Seiffert, Peter; Popp, Lucia; Hubbard, Freddie; Williams, Robin (Robin Douglas)
  - Concert/Booking Files, 1992-1993 Season:, 39 folders (Box 317)
    Folders contain various materials including programs, correspondence, contracts, clippings, reviews, photographs, fliers, and other records related to each performance. [Folders:] (1) Horacio Gutiérrez; (2) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (3) Aprile Millo; (4) Russian National Orchestra [Mikhail Pletnev, conductor]/Ivo Pogorelich; (5) Michael Flatley/Battlefield Band; (6) Big Band Salute to Glenn Miller [The Modernaires with Paula Kelly, Jr.; Beryl Davis; Dick Haymes, Jr.; Rex Allen and His Orchestra]; (7) Camerata Musica of Berlin; (8) Gary Lakes; (9) Opera in Concert [Los Angeles Concert Opera Association, Kalman's "Countess Maritza"]; (10) Ballet Folclórico Nacional de México; (11) 15th Air Force Band [of the Golden West]; (12) Mel Tormé with Trio; (13) Big Band Salute to Glenn Miller, Big Sandy, Texas [The Modernaires with Paula Kelly, Jr.; Beryl Davis; Dick Haymes, Jr.; Rex Allen and His Orchestra]; (14) the King's Singers; (15) Howdee Meyers [& Lucia Perrigo], "Come to the Castle" [travelogue]; (16) Mark O'Connor; (17) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (18) [Michael] Newman & [Laura] Oltman; (19) Pasadena Roof Orchestra; (20) Elisso Bolkvadze; (21) Paco Peña; (22) Big Band Dance Nights; (23) Americus Brass Band; (24) Dmitri Berlinsky; (25) American Ballroom Theatre; (26) Don Cossack Dancers; (27) Thayer Soule, "Railroads Are Fun" [travelogue]; (28) Little Eagles of Siberia; (29) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (30) St. Louis Symphony Orchestra/Leonard Slatkin; (31) Howard Alden; (32) P.U.S.D. [Pasadena Unified School District]; (33) Dave McKenna; (34) Harolyn Blackwell; (35) James Galway/Kazuhito Yamashita; (36) [Hiroko Nakamura]; (37) Boston Camerata; (38) José Greco Spanish Dance Company; (39) Harold C. Schonberg, "Great Pianists" lecture.
    Modernaires (Musical group); Kelly, Paula; King’s Singers (Vocal group); Ballet Folklórico de México; Tormé, Mel; Lakes, Gary; Los Angeles Concert Opera; Nakamura, Hiroko; Millo, Aprile; Boston Camerata; Gutiérrez, Horacio; José Greco Company; Flatley, Michael; Schonberg, Harold C.; Battlefield Band; McKenna, Dave; Pogorelich, Ivo; Blackwell, Harolyn; Pletnev, Mikhail; Galway, James; Davis, Beryl; Yamashita, Kazuhito; Rossiĭskiĭ nat︠s︡ionalʹnyĭ orkestr; Péña, Paco; American Ballroom Theater; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Berlinsky, Dmitri; Gosudarstvennyĭ ansamblʹ pesni i pli︠a︡ski donskikh kazakov; Soule, Thayer; Slatkin, Leonard; Alden, Howard; St. Louis Symphony Orchestra; Camerata Musica-Berlin; Bolkvadze, Eliso; Pasadena Roof Orchestra; Oltman, Laura; Newman, Michael; Newman & Oltman Guitar Duo; O'Connor, Mark; Americus Brass Band
  - Concert/Booking Files, 1992-1993 Season:, 39 folders (Box 318)
    Folders contain various materials including programs, correspondence, contracts, clippings, reviews, photographs, fliers, and other records related to each performance. [Folders:] (1) Dmitri Ratser; (2) [William] Bolcom & [Joan] Morris; (3) Krasnayarsk; (4) Meridian Arts Ensemble; (5) Juilliard String Quartet; (6) Mark Whitfield; (7) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (8) Elmar Oliveira/Horacio Gutierrez; (9) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (10) River City Brass Band; (11) Jerry Hadley; (12) Ivo Pogorelich; (13) Julian Bream; (14) Clay Francisco, "Rivers of France" [travelogue]; (15) Gail Niwa; (16) [Albert] McNeil Jubilee Singers; (17) Academy of St. Martin in the Fields/Christopher Parkening/Iona Brown; (18) Don McLean; (19) Naumburg Chamber Competition Winner, Eroica Trio; (20) Andre Watts; (21) Opera A La Carte; (22) Don Cornell/Helen O'Connell; (23) Calliope; (24) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (25) Marc Teicholz; (26) P.Y.S.O. [Pasadena Youth Symphony Orchestra]; (27) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (28) Sherrill Milnes; (29) Zachary Opera Finals [Concert]; (30) P.Y.M.O. [Pasadena Young Musicians Orchestra]; (31) Manuel Barrueco & Nancy Allen; (32) Stanley Turrentine Quartet; (33) Johnson Mountain Boys [replaced the Dillards] and Peter Rowan; (34) Doug Jones, "The Great Alaska Cruise" [travelogue]; (35) Glenn Yarbrough & the Limeliters; (36) California & John Hartford; (37) Empire Brass; (38) 1993 Van Cliburn Competition Winner [Simone Pedroni]; (39) Young Soloists with Los Angeles Metropolitan Opera.
    Jones, Doug; Parkening, Christopher; Rowan, Peter (guitarist); Rat︠s︡er, Dmitriĭ; Johnson Mountain Boys; Bolcom, William; Dillards; Morris, Joan; Niwa, Gail; O'Connell, Helen; California (Musical group); Albert McNeil Jubilee Singers; Limeliters (Musical group); Academy of St. Martin-in-the-Fields; Yarbrough, Glenn; Brown, Iona; Teicholz, Marc; Calliope (Musical group); Pedroni, Simone; Empire Brass (Musical group); Turrentine, Stanley; Allen, Nancy; Barrueco, Manuel; Milnes, Sherrill; Bream, Julian; McLean, Don; Hadley, Jerry; Pogorelich, Ivo; Opera A La Carte; Hartford, John; Cornell, Don; Eroica Trio; Watts, Andre; Juilliard String Quartet; Whitfield, Mark; Francisco, Clay; Meridian Arts Ensemble; Oliveira, Elmar; River City Brass Band; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Gutiérrez, Horacio
  - Concert/Booking Files, Pasadena Jazz Festival:, 1991 -- 1993; 31 folders (Box 319)
    Folders contain various materials related to the Pasadena Jazz Festival, including programs, correspondence, contracts, clippings, reviews, photographs, fliers, and other records related to concert performances and other features of the festival, such as the sale of food and souvenirs. [Folders:] (1-2) 1991 [Pasadena] Jazz Festival; (3) Claude Bolling Big Band; (4) John Stowell [Trio]; (5) the Harper Brothers [Winard and Philip]; (6) Poncho Sanchez; (7) Dizzy Gillespie; (8-9) 1992 Pasadena Jazz Festival; (10) 1992 Pasadena Jazz Festival (Chuck Niles, restaurants, reviews, CD/video sales); (11) Lee Ritenour; (12) Arturo Sandoval; (13) Eliane Elias Trio; (14) Gene Harris Quartet; (15) Milt Jackson [replaced Lionel Hampton]; (16) Swing Savant; (17-20) 1993 Pasadena Jazz Festival; (21) 1993 Pasadena Jazz Festival (Pitch Package/Welcome Package); (22) 1993 Pasadena Jazz Festival (Reviews); (23) 1993 Pasadena Jazz Festival ([Performer] Bios/Restaurants); (24) Dori Caymmi, Ivan Lins, Ricardo Silveira; (25) Clayton-Hamilton Jazz Orchestra; (26) Chuck Niles, Master of Ceremonies; (27) Diane Schuur; (28) Hendrik Meurkens; (29) Ken Peplowski Quintet; (30) Black Note; (31) Dave & Don Grusin.
    Caymmi, Dori; Grusin, Don; Silveira, Ricardo; Lins, Ivan; Schuur, Diane; Clayton-Hamilton Jazz Orchestra; Elias, Eliane; Meurkens, Hendrik; Grusin, Dave; Ken Peplowski Quintet; Peplowski, Ken; Bolling, Claude; Pasadena Jazz Festival; Stowell, John, guitarist; Claude Bolling Big Band; Jackson, Milt; Gene Harris Quartet; Harris, Gene; Niles, Chuck; Gillespie, Dizzy; Sandoval, Arturo; Ritenour, Lee; Harper, Philip; Harper Brothers; Sanchez, Poncho; Harper, Winard
  - Concert/Booking Files, 1993-1994 Season:, 39 folders (Box 320)
    Folders contain various materials including programs, correspondence, contracts, clippings, reviews, photographs, fliers, and other records related to each performance. [Folders:] (1) 1993-1994 Season - General; (2) 1993-1994 Season - L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra] General; (3) Disney's Young Musicians Symphony Orchestra Filming; (4) James Morris; (5) Jack Jones; (6) Joaquin Achucarro; (7) Charlie Haden's Quartet West; (8) Andre Watts and Friends; (9) James Whitmore [as Will Rogers]; (10) Maxim Mogilevsky; (11) Tex Beneke & the Four Freshmen; (12) Emmylou Harris [and the Nash Ramblers]; (13) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (14) Sherilyn Mentes, "The Kingdom of Netherlands" [travelogue]; (15) Judy Carmichael; (16) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (17) June Anderson; (18) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (19) Chestnut Brass Band [Company]; (20) Carlos Barbosa-Lima; (21) Cleo Laine & John Dankworth; (22) Peter Serkin & Pamela Frank; (23) New England Ragtime Ensemble [Gunther Schuller]; (24) Royal Regiments on Parade; (25) Naumburg Violin Competition Winner [Tomohiro Okumura]; (26) Andrea Lucchesini; (27) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (28) Guarneri Quartet; (29) Texas Piano Professors [Carole Fran, Erbie Bowser, Smokie Rhodes, Marcia Ball]; (30) Naumburg Chamber Competition Winner, Cavani String Quartet; (31) Frederica von Stade; (32) Brandenburg Collegium; (33) L.A.C.O. [Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra]; (34) Juan Serrano; (35) [Ivo] Pogorelich [International Solo Piano] Competition; (36) San Marino Guild Lectures; (37) Concord Jazz All-Stars [Scott Hamilton, Howard Alden, Gerry Wiggins]; (38) Doug Jones, "The Great Canadian Train Ride" [travelogue]; (39) Big Band '94 with Guy Lombardo's Royal Canadians [Pied Pipers, Gary Crosby].
    Laine, Cleo; Schuller, Gunther; New England Ragtime Ensemble; Guarneri Quartet; Lucchesini, Andrea; Okumura, Tomohiro; Cavani Quartet; Von Stade, Frederica; Ball, Marcia; Jones, Jack; Bowser, Erbie; Achucarro, Joaquin; Fran, Carol; Morris, James; Brandenburg Collegium; Mentes, Sherilyn; Serrano, Juan; Ivo Pogorelich International Solo Piano Competition; Los Angeles Chamber Orchestra; Crosby, Gary; Pied Pipers (Musical group); Harris, Emmylou; Jones, Doug; Four Freshmen (Musical group); Royal Canadians (Musical group); Beneke, Tex; Hamilton, Scott; Mogilevsky, Maxim; Wiggins, Gerald; Whitmore, James; Concord All Stars; Watts, Andre; Alden, Howard; Quartet West; Haden, Charlie; Dankworth, John; Serkin, Peter, 1947-; Frank, Pamela; Carmichael, Judy; Anderson, June; Chestnut Brass Company (Musical group); Barbosa-Lima, Carlos; Nash Ramblers
  - Concert/Booking Files, 1993-1994 Season:, 37 folders (Box 321)